{
    "subject": "resource/Rafael_Ara\u00fajo_(basketball)",
    "predicate": "ontology/college",
    "object": "resource/BYU_Cougars_men's_basketball",
    "human_readable": "Rafael Ara\u00fajo (basketball) attended BYU Cougars men's basketball.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9662444591522217,
            "question": "What is Rafael Ara\u00fajo's connection to BYU Cougars men's basketball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8926133513450623,
            "question": "Which university's men's basketball program did Rafael Ara\u00fajo play for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565676808357239,
            "question": "Is Rafael Ara\u00fajo associated with BYU?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7731509804725647,
            "question": "What was the name of the basketball team Rafael Ara\u00fajo played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7489023208618164,
            "question": "Was Rafael Ara\u00fajo part of a college basketball team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6472901105880737,
            "question": "What sport is Rafael Ara\u00fajo known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6472465395927429,
            "question": "Did Rafael Ara\u00fajo play basketball at the collegiate level?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324866414070129,
            "question": "What kind of player was Rafael Ara\u00fajo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5042715668678284,
            "question": "Where did Rafael Ara\u00fajo attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.468838095664978,
            "question": "In what sport did Rafael Ara\u00fajo participate in college?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rafael Ara\u00fajo (basketball) attended BYU Cougars men's basketball.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5236_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Rafael Ara\u00fajo attend college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5236_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of player was Rafael Ara\u00fajo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5236_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Rafael Ara\u00fajo play basketball at the collegiate level?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5236_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5236_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate the triple, I need to check if the information in the documents supports the statement \"Rafael Ara\u00fajo (basketball) attended BYU Cougars men's basketball\".\n\nAfter analyzing the documents, I can confirm that Rafael Araujo is indeed a former player of the BYU Cougars men's basketball team. The documents mention his achievements and records while playing for the team.\n\nTherefore, the output is:\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Rafael Araujo's time at Brigham Young University (BYU), confirming his attendance and significant contributions to the BYU Cougars men's basketball team."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}